$(document).ready(function () {

    var quizArray = [{
        question: "What City Are the Heat in?",
        answer: ["Baltimore", "Paris", "Orlando", "Miami"],
        correct: ["Miami"]
    }, {
        question: "How Many championships have the Boston Celtics won?",
        answer: ["0", "18", "7", "21"],
        correct: ["21"]
    }, {
        question: "Who does Steph Curry play for",
        answer: ["Lakers", "Warriors", "Knicks", "Cleveland"],
        correct: ["Warriors"]
    }, {
        question: "How many points did Kobe score in his last game?",
        answer: ["24", "8", "45", "60"],
        correct: ["60"]
    },{
        question: "Who won the NBA Championship in 2018?",
        answer: ["Warriors", "Kobe", "Spurs", "Thunder"],
        correct: ["Warriors"]
    },
    {
        question: "How Many Teams Are in the NBA?",
        answer: ["3", "25", "30", "33"],
        correct: ["30"]
    },{
        question: "How Many Games does each team play at home?",
        answer: ["50", "41", "20", "82"],
        correct: ["41"]
    },{
        question: "How many feet high is Basketball rim?",
        answer: ["10 feet", "25 feet", "20 feet", "1 feet"],
        correct: ["10 feet"]
    },{
        question: "Which player has score 100 points in a game?",
        answer: ["Wilt Chaimberlain", "Kobe Bryant", "Lebron James", "Kevin Durant"],
        correct: ["Wilt Chaimberlain"]
    },{
        question: "What year was the Lakers last championship?",
        answer: ["2003", "1993", "2010", "2005"],
        correct: ["2010"]
     }];

     console.log(quizArray.question); 





});